emlovz.com 2013-11-21

# EmLovz | Privacy | EmLovz Personal Dating Coach for Men

**Privacy**

Thank you for visiting EmLovz.com. Your privacy a high priority to us. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in the privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for EmLovz.com only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific requests. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

EmLovz.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gather information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors on the Site, and understanding how our visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents, and contractors (who have also agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Login Privacy**

We have chosen to use WordPress login to create a more social experience for our users; also to make it convenient for our clients to continue to access our page. By default, when you log in to our website, your browsing of our website will not be made public. 

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us by email at [info@emlovz.com](mailto:info@emlovz.com).
